But I think this is
definitely something to behold.  And then comes
a heatwave.  That's insane.  I'd
say put the charcoal on, then the grill grate on top.
That shows you how much heat is
generated.  It turns blue.
That's why we'll wait a little longer.  If
we were to make campfire bread, it would also be ideal
for children, because with that their eyes burn, but
not with this one.  We have to
wait until the temperature drops a little
.  Ideal for steak
.  Absolute heat.  Exactly what
we need.  But
a bit too much for bratwurst.  But that
also means we don't
need nearly as much money as I've
poured in.  Okay, the sausage can go
on right away.  Which is fascinating.
Look how cleanly it
's burned.  Nothing is left.  In
comparison, with a fire bowl where the
ash simply lies on the ground,
here it actually lies underneath,
but surprisingly there is relatively little
ash and you have an enormous
grilling surface.  This is insane.  What
I would have really liked is
a small edge so that if you
roll something, it doesn't roll off.  You
always have to remain critical, right?
Because I'm not an influencer, I'm a
product tester, but I think this is
definitely worth seeing and it's generating a lot of
heat.  That's insane.   That's
ten times more than at a campfire.
Ten times more pleasant without smoke.